pointdoubler.com 2010-09-26

# None

Welcome to the PointDoubler web site (www.pointdoubler.com). PointDoubler values the privacy of the users, subscribers, members, and others who visit and use the PointDoubler Platform (collectively or individually, "you" or "Users"). By using the PointDoubler Platform, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, please do not use the PointDoubler Platform. This Privacy Policy should be read in connection with the PointDoubler Terms of Use. Your use of the PointDoubler Platform and any personal information you provide through the PointDoubler Platform are subject at all time to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. 

##  1\. The Information PointDoubler Collects 

User-provided Information: You may provide to PointDoubler what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, email address, postal mailing address, telephone number and billing information) if you upload or download certain content or products from the PointDoubler Platform, enter contests or sweepstakes, take advantage of promotions, respond to surveys, register and subscribe for certain services, or otherwise use the features and functionality of the PointDoubler Platform. You may also provide to PointDoubler demographic information and information related to your favorite social networking site such as the name, address and description. "Cookies" Information: When you access the PointDoubler Platform, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. PointDoubler may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the PointDoubler Platform. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by PointDoubler only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. "Automatically Collected" Information: When you access the PointDoubler Platform or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique user ID, version of software installed, system type, screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords, JavaScript enablement, the content and pages that you access on the PointDoubler Platform, and the dates and times that you visit the PointDoubler Platform, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages. 

##  2\. Web Beacons 

Our web pages may contain electronic image requests (called a "single-pixel gif" or "web beacon" request) that allow us to count page views and to access cookies. Any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. Web beacons are typically 1-by-1 pixel files, but their presence can usually be seen within a browser by clicking on "View" and then on "Source." We may also include web beacons in HTML-formatted newsletters that we send to opt-in subscribers in order to count how many newsletters have been read. PointDoubler web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personally identifiable information about our web site visitors, they are just the technique we use to compile anonymous information about web site usage. 

##  3\. The Way PointDoubler Uses Information 

PointDoubler uses the information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the PointDoubler Platform, to allow us to charge and invoice you, as well as to track user-generated content and Users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major PointDoubler Platform updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the PointDoubler Platform. PointDoubler uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the PointDoubler Platform works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. PointDoubler may use "Automatically Collected" information and "Cookies" information to: (a) automatically update the PointDoubler application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the PointDoubler Platform; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities 

##  4\. When PointDoubler Discloses Information 

PointDoubler does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the PointDoubler Platform or related sites becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction. We may disclose some limited User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; validate credit card numbers; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist PointDoubler in improving the PointDoubler Platform and creating new services features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures. PointDoubler may share aggregate statistical information gathered from you and other Users with advertisers, business partners, sponsor or other third parties. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of visitors visited a certain area on a web site or that Y number of men and Z number PointDoubler may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the manner required by the requesting entity. PointDoubler also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect PointDoubler from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the PointDoubler Platform; enforce the Terms of Use; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of PointDoubler, our Users, or others. 

##  5\. Your Choices 

You may, of course, decline to share your personally-identifiable information with PointDoubler, in which case PointDoubler will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the PointDoubler Platform. You may update, correct, or delete your user information and preferences on the account information page under "My Account - Account Settings". We recommend you do not divulge your account password to anyone. PointDoubler will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited telephone call or e-mail. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES. 

##  6\. Our Commitment to Data Security 

PointDoubler uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to PointDoubler, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, PointDoubler makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If PointDoubler learns of a security systems breach, then we will attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. PointDoubler may post a notice on the PointDoubler Platform if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at support@pointdoubler.com 

##  7\. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy 

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE POINTDOUBLER PLATFORM AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, PointDoubler does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If PointDoubler learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on or through the PointDoubler Platform, then PointDoubler will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who uses the PointDoubler Platform, then please contact PointDoubler at support@pointdoubler.com to have that child's information deleted. The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your children's access to certain types of material on the Internet. While PointDoubler does not endorse these resources, we provide information about them as a public service to our community. â€¢ "OnGuard Online," maintained by the Federal Trade Commission â€¢ WiredSafety â€¢ Netsmartz.org â€¢ The Child Safety Network â€¢ Control Kids â€¢ Cyber Sitter â€¢ Net Nanny 

##  8\. International Visitors 

For Users visiting the PointDoubler Platform from the European Economic Area or other non-U.S. territories, please note that any data you enter into the PointDoubler Platform will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or such other non-U.S. territory for use by PointDoubler and its affiliates for any of the purposes described herein. In addition, because PointDoubler operates globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and affiliates. By providing any data on the PointDoubler Platform, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries. 

##  9\. In the Event of Merger or Sale 

In the event that PointDoubler is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

##  10\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by a "last modified" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the PointDoubler Platform constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you (e.g. by email or by means of a notice on our homepage) and obtain your consent before implementing revisions with respect to such information. 

##  11\. Effective Date, Date Last Modified 

Privacy Policy effective as of February 3, 2009. Privacy Policy last modified on February 3, 2009. 

##  12\. Unsolicited E-mails 

PointDoubler does not send unsolicited e-mails to non-public addresses or to anyone who has asked us not to contact him or her. Any newsletters that we send are only sent to those who have subscribed to them. To stop receiving e-mails or newsletters from PointDoubler, click on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail or newsletter. 

##  13\. PointDoubler Contact Information 

PointDoubler is owned and operated by Lucky Pacific Networks, Llc. Please contact Lucky Pacific with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: Lucky Pacific Networks, Llc, 115 Everett Avenue, Third Floor, Palo Alto, California, 94301, USA or by email at: support@pointdoubler.com. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.
